<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fiona</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_chat">ChatActivity</string>


    <string name="terms">
 \n \n
        Terms of Service \n
EFFECTIVE DATE: October 24, 2017 \n \n
These Fiona Terms of Service (the \"Terms\") are a legal contract between you and Fiona, Inc. (\"Fiona\", \"we\" or \"us\"). These Terms explain how you are permitted to use the Fiona mobile application and services, and any content therein (collectively, the \"Services\"). Unless otherwise specified, all references to the Services include the services available through the Fiona mobile application (the \"App\") and the Site, as well as any software that Fiona provides to you that allows you to access the Services from a mobile device and any other Materials (as defined below). By using the Services, you are agreeing to all of the Terms; if you do not agree with any of these Terms, do not access or otherwise use the Services.
\n \n
Changes \n
Fiona may make changes to the Services at any time. Fiona can change, update, or add or remove provisions of these Terms at any time by posting the updated Terms on the App or the Site, by posting a notice on the Services or by notifying you via the App. By using the Services after Fiona has updated the Terms, you are agreeing to all the updated Terms; if you do not agree with any of the updated Terms, you must stop using Services.
 \n \n
General Use \n
The Services may not be available in all locations, and we may block access to the Services from certain locations based on your device’s geolocation information. We may add to or remove the areas in which the Services are not available at any time, without notice to you.
By using, you represent, acknowledge and agree that you are at least 18 years of age. If you are not at least 18 years old, you may not use the Services at any time or in any manner or submit any information to the App, the Site or any part of the Services.
We may, in our sole discretion, refuse to offer the Services to any person or entity. We may, without notice and in our sole discretion, terminate your right to use the Services, or any portion thereof, and block or prevent your future access to and use of the Services or any portion thereof.
 \n \n
Services \n
Fiona provides content through the Services that is copyrighted and&#47;or trademarked work of Fiona or Fiona’s third-party licensors and suppliers or other users of the Services (collectively, the \"Materials\"). Materials may include logos, text graphics, video, images, photos, software and other content.
Subject to these Terms, Fiona hereby grants you a limited, non-exclusive, non-sublicensable, non-transferable and revocable license to use and to display the Materials and to use the Services solely for your personal, non-commercial use. Except for the foregoing license, you have no other rights in the Services or any Materials and you may not modify, edit, copy, reproduce, create derivative works of, reverse engineer, alter, enhance or in any way exploit any of the Services or Materials in any manner.
You may use the App for one registered account on one mobile device owned or leased solely by you, for your personal, non-commercial use. You may not: (i) modify, disassemble, decompile or reverse engineer the App, except to the extent that such restriction is expressly prohibited by law; (ii) rent, lease, loan, resell, sublicense, distribute or otherwise transfer the App to any third-party or use the App to provide time sharing or similar services for any third-party; (iii) make any copies of the App; (iv) remove, circumvent, disable, damage or otherwise interfere with security-related features of the App, features that prevent or restrict use or copying of any content accessible through the App, or features that enforce limitations on use of the App; or (v) delete the copyright and other proprietary rights notices on the App. You acknowledge that Fiona may from time to time issue upgraded versions of the App, and may automatically electronically upgrade the version of the App that you are using on your mobile device. You consent to such automatic upgrading on your mobile device, and agree that these Terms will apply to all such upgrades. Standard carrier data charges may apply to your use of the App.
Except for the limited rights expressly licensed in these Terms, Fiona and its third-party licensors or suppliers retain all right, title, and interest in and to the Services.
 \n \n
The following additional terms and conditions apply with respect to any App that Fiona provides to you designed for use on an Apple iOS-powered mobile device (an \"iOS App\"):
You acknowledge that these Terms are between you and Fiona only, and not with Apple, Inc. (\"Apple\").
Your use of Fiona’s iOS App must comply with Apple\'s then-current App Store Terms of Service.
Fiona, and not Apple, are solely responsible for our iOS App and the Services and Content available thereon. You acknowledge that Apple has no obligation to provide maintenance and support services with respect to our iOS App. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, Apple will have no warranty obligation whatsoever with respect to our iOS App.
You agree that Fiona, and not Apple, are responsible for addressing any claims by you or any third-party relating to our iOS App or your possession and&#47;or use of our iOS App.
You agree that Fiona, and not Apple, shall be responsible, to the extent required by these Terms, for the investigation, defense, settlement and discharge of any third-party intellectual property infringement claim related to our iOS App or your possession and use of our iOS App.
You represent and warrant that (i) you are not located in a country that is subject to a U.S. Government embargo, or that has been designated by the U.S. Government as a \"terrorist supporting\" country; and (ii) You are not listed on any U.S. Government list of prohibited or restricted parties.
You agree to comply with all applicable third-party terms of agreement when using our iOS App (e.g., you must not be in violation of your wireless data service terms of agreement when using the iOS App).
The parties agree that Apple and Apple\'s subsidiaries are third-party beneficiaries to these Terms as they relate to your license of Fiona\'s iOS App. Upon your acceptance of these Terms, Apple will have the right (and will be deemed to have accepted the right) to enforce these Terms against you as they relate to your license of the iOS App as a third-party beneficiary thereof.
If you breach any of these Terms, the above license will terminate automatically and you must immediately stop using the Services and destroy any downloaded or printed Materials.
 \n \n
Account Security \n
We may ask for your mobile number in order to verify your account when you try to post content or if we suspect improper activity on your account. Please note that your carrier\'s text messaging and data fees apply for mobile number verification.
 \n \n
Privacy \n
Please review the Fiona Privacy Policy (the \"Privacy Policy\"). By using our Services, you agree that we may use and disclose the information we collect from and about you as stated in the Privacy Policy (which is incorporated into these Terms). Without limiting the foregoing, you expressly acknowledge that any Submissions (defined below) or other information you submit to the Services may be viewable by all other users of the Services and any third party.
Submissions
You are responsible for any information, handles, profiles, statuses, opinions, messages, comments, photos, videos, graphics, sounds and other content or material that you submit, upload, post or otherwise make available on, through or in connection with the Services (each a \"Submission\") . When you provide Submissions you agree that those Submissions shall not be in violation of the \"Unauthorized Activities\" section below. Although Fiona may, in its sole discretion, monitor, screen, modify, refuse, remove or edit Submissions for any reason, Fiona is not obligated to do so. You have full responsibility for each Submission you make, including its legality, reliability and appropriateness and will be solely liable for any damage or harm resulting from your Submissions.
We may retain your Submissions, even after they have expired from view within the Services or even after you have deleted them. However, you agree that we have no obligation to retain any Submission for any period of time, nor shall we be responsible or liable to you or any third party for any lost content or losses related to the expiration or deletion of a Submission.
Unless otherwise explicitly stated herein or in the Privacy Policy, you agree that any Submission provided by you in connection with the Services is provided on a non-proprietary and non-confidential basis. You hereby grant to Fiona a non-exclusive, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, fully paid-up, worldwide license (including the right to sublicense through multiple tiers) to use, reproduce, process, adapt, publicly perform, publicly display, modify, prepare derivative works, publish, transmit and distribute each of your Submissions, or any portion thereof, in any form, medium or distribution method now known or hereafter existing, known or developed, and authorize others to do the same (\"Submission License\"). Without limiting the foregoing, you agree that the Submission License gives Fiona the right to sublicense Submissions to third parties in connection with the syndication, broadcast, distribution, promotion, or publication of Submissions in any and all media or distribution methods, now known or later developed. No use of Submissions in accordance with the Submission License shall entitle you to any compensation from Fiona, or any third party. You agree to pay for all royalties, fees, damages and any other monies owing any person by reason of any Submissions posted by you to or through the Services.
 \n \n
Unauthorized Activities \n
When using the Services, you agree not to:
Create a handle for the purpose of preventing others from using that handle.
Sell or buy handles.
Impersonate another person in a manner that is intended to or does mislead, confuse or deceive others.
Post or share another individual\'s private information without their express authorization and permission.
Defame, abuse, bully, harass, stalk, threaten, or otherwise violate the legal rights of others.
Use racially or ethnically offensive language.
Discuss or incite illegal activity.
Post or share Submissions that contain pornography or graphic violence.
Post or share anything that exploits children or minors or that depicts cruelty to animals.
Post or share Submissions that violate any third party right, including any copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, moral right, privacy right, right of publicity or any other intellectual property or proprietary right.
Disseminate any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, \'junk mail\', \'spam\', \'chain letters\', \'pyramid schemes\', or any other form of such solicitation.
Use any robot, spider, crawler, scraper or other automated means to access the Services.
Take any action that imposes an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on our infrastructure.
Use or develop any third party applications that interact with the Services or Submissions without our prior written consent.
Alter the opinions or comments posted by others on the Services.
Post or share any image or language that is obscene, vulgar or offensive or that threatens, disparages or demeans any individual or group.
Attempt to circumvent any of our content-filtering techniques.
Post or share anything inappropriate or disruptive to the Services.
Disrupt, negatively affect or inhibit users from having a positive experience with the Services.
Use the Services in violation of these Terms and&#47;or for any unlawful purposes.
Post or share anything contrary to our public image, goodwill or reputation.
This list of prohibitions provides examples and is not exhaustive or exclusive. Fiona reserves the right to (a) suspend or terminate access to your account and your ability to post to the Services (or otherwise use the Services), (b) delete, remove or refuse to distribute any Submissions and&#47;or &#169; reclaim handles, all with or without cause and with or without notice, for any reason or no reason without liability to you. If Fiona believes a Submission violates these Terms, it may make that Submission invisible to other users without notifying you. Your Submission will be visible to you, but will not appear for any other user. Fiona may report to law enforcement authorities any actions that may be illegal, and any reports it receives of such conduct.  When legally required or at Fiona\'s discretion, Fiona will cooperate with law enforcement agencies in any investigation of alleged illegal activity on the Services or on the Internet.
Unauthorized use of any Materials or Third-Party Content contained in the Services may violate certain laws and regulations. You agree to indemnify and hold Fiona and its officers, directors, employees, consultants, affiliates, agents, licensors, and business partners (collectively, the \"Indemnified Entities\") harmless from and against any and all costs, damages, liabilities, and expenses (including attorneys\' fees and costs of defense) Fiona or any other Indemnified Entity suffers in relation to, arising from, or for the purpose of avoiding, any claim or demand from a third party that your use of the Services or the use of the Services by any person using your user name and&#47;or password violates any applicable law or regulation, or the copyrights, trademark rights or other rights of any third party.
 \n \n
Disclaimer of Warranties \n
Your use of the Services is at your own risk. The Materials may not have been verified or authenticated in whole or in part by Fiona, and they may include inaccuracies or typographical or other errors. Fiona does not warrant the accuracy of timeliness of the Materials contained on the Services. Fiona has no liability for any loss of, or errors or omissions in Submissions, or for any errors or omissions in the Materials or any other portion of the Services, whether provided by Fiona, our licensors or suppliers or other users.
Fiona, FOR ITSELF AND ITS LICENSORS, MAKES NO EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES, OR GUARANTEES IN CONNECTION WITH THE SERVICES OR ANY MATERIALS RELATING TO THE QUALITY, SUITABILITY, TRUTH, ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF ANY INFORMATION OR MATERIAL CONTAINED OR PRESENTED ON THE SERVICES. UNLESS OTHERWISE EXPLICITLY STATED, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE SERVICES, MATERIALS AND ANY OTHER PORTION OF THE SERVICES OR ANY INFORMATION OR MATERIAL CONTAINED OR PRESENTED ON THE SERVICES IS PROVIDED TO YOU ON AN \"AS IS,\" \"AS AVAILABLE\" BASIS WITH NO WARRANTY OF IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, Fiona DOES NOT PROVIDE ANY WARRANTIES AGAINST VIRUSES, SPYWARE OR MALWARE THAT MAY BE INSTALLED ON YOUR COMPUTER.
 \n \n
Limitation of Liability \n
IN NO EVENT WILL Fiona BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES EVEN IF Fiona HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, Fiona SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DAMAGES RESULTING FROM YOUR DISPLAYING, COPYING, OR DOWNLOADING ANY MATERIALS TO OR FROM THE SERVICES.
YOU ASSUME TOTAL RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES. YOUR ONLY REMEDY AGAINST Fiona FOR DISSATISFACTION WITH THE SERVICES IS TO STOP USING THE SERVICES. IF, NOTWITHSTANDING THESE TERMS, Fiona IS FOUND LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DAMAGE OR LOSS THAT ARISES OUT OF OR IS IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES, Fiona\'S LIABILITY SHALL IN NO EVENT EXCEED ONE U.S. DOLLAR ($1.00) IN THE AGGREGATE.
THE FOREGOING EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS SHALL APPLY TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY, SO THE FOREGOING EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
 \n \n
Local Laws; Export Control. \n
Fiona controls and operates the Services from its headquarters in the United States and the Services may not be appropriate or available for use in other locations. You are responsible for following applicable laws and regulations in your jurisdiction, including but not limited to laws and regulations regarding the transmission of technical data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside.
 \n \n
Feedback \n
If you send or transmit any communications, comments, questions, suggestions, or related materials regarding Fiona or the Services, whether by email otherwise (collectively, \"Feedback\"), such Feedback is, and will be treated as, non-confidential and non-proprietary. You hereby assign all right, title, and interest in, and Fiona is free to use, without any attribution or compensation to you, any and all Feedback for any purpose whatsoever. You understand and agree that Fiona is not obligated to use, display, reproduce, or distribute any such ideas, know-how, concepts, or techniques contained in the Feedback, and you have no right to compel such use, display, reproduction, or distribution.
 \n \n
General \n
The applicable U.S. federal law and State law, without regard to the choice or conflicts of law provisions, will govern these Terms. Foreign laws do not apply. The United Nations on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods and any laws based on the Uniform Computer Information Transactions Act (UCITA) shall not apply to this Agreement.  If any of these Terms is found to be inconsistent with applicable law, then such term shall be interpreted to reflect the intentions of the parties, and no other terms will be modified. Fiona\'s failure to enforce any of these Terms is not a waiver of such term. These Terms are the entire agreement between you and Fiona and supersede all prior or contemporaneous negotiations, discussions or agreements between you and Fiona about the Services. The proprietary rights, disclaimer of warranties, representations made by you, indemnities, limitations of liability and general provisions shall survive any termination of these Terms.
 \n \n
Copyright Policy \n
Fiona respects the intellectual property rights of others. If you believe that your intellectual property appears on the Services in violation of your copyright, please provide Fiona\'s designated agent the following information:
A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
Identification of the work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site.
Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled at the Services, and information reasonably sufficient to permit Fiona to locate the material.
Information reasonably sufficient to permit Fiona to contact you as the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic mail address at which you may be contacted.
A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the intellectual property owner, its agent, or the law.
A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
Fiona\'s agent for notice of claims of intellectual property infringement on the Services can be reached as follows:

We will notify you that we have removed or disabled access to copyright-protected material that you provided, if such removal is pursuant to a valid DMCA take-down notice that we have received. If you receive such notice from us, you may provide us with a counter-notification in writing to Fiona that includes all of the following information:
Your physical or electronic signature;
Identification of the material that has been removed or to which access has been disabled, and the location at which the material appeared before it was removed or access to it was disabled;
A statement from you under the penalty of perjury, that you have a good faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of a mistake or misidentification; and
Your name, physical address and telephone number, and a statement that you consent to the jurisdiction of a court for the judicial district in which your physical address is located, or if your physical address is outside of the United States, for any judicial district in which Fiona may be located, and that you will accept service of process from the person who provided notification of allegedly infringing material or an agent of such person.

    </string>
</resources>
